Understanding the user's mentality far outweighs the number of tests written.

### **PROFILE**

QA automation engineer with a passion for hi-fi audio. Experienced mapping test plans and enhancing existing suites in an Agile environment. Over the last 3 years, recorded and mixed albums for both unknown and prominent musicians, such as David Bowie, Rakim, and The Roots.

TECH

JavaScript, Python, SQL. Jasmine, Mocha, Selenium, WebdriverlO, Postman, SoapUl, BrowserStack, Appium. RESTful APIs.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### **AUDIO ENGINEER**, Queens, NY

GB's Juke Joint Recording Studio, Forrest Sound & Vision

2018 - Present

- Recorded and mixed a variety of musicians, communicating with artists to determine aesthetic and appropriate recording techniques. Managed and debugged sessions with complex signal flows utilizing multiple audio technologies (CoreAudio, AoIP, etc).
- Worked with Burl Audio to test and quantify sample rate and delay issues in their analog-todigital convertors, helping them add a whole new subset of users to their market base.

#### **AUTOMATION ENGINEER**, Hoboken, NJ

TriAd Media Solutions

2017 - 2018

- Architected and led test planning and automation (JavaScript) for a higher-education web marketing platform with no prior testing infrastructure.
- Wrote feature and end-to-end tests designed to cover thousands of permutations across UI and API (Jasmine, Selenium).

#### **AUTOMATION ENGINEER**, New York, NY

globaledit

2015 - 2017

- Planned and executed UI and API automation test suites (JavaScript) across web, mobile, and iOS for a Digital Asset Management platform.
- Established a pace of same-sprint automation delivery using frameworks that drastically improved regression testing efficiency across multiple devices and browsers (Mocha, Chai, WebdriverIO, BrowserStack).

## **QA ENGINEER**, New York, NY

JOOR

2014 - 2015

- Responsible for all testing aspects of an enterprise iPad app in a start-up environment.
  Communicated with users to profile behavior, creating more efficient test cases and informing future product development.
- Leveraged test automation (Python) to scale testing alongside a rapidly growing feature-set and user-base. Tracked usage data (SQL and Localytics) to enhance product team's insights.

# **EDUCATION**

# WASHINGTON AND LEE UNIVERSITY, Lexington, VA

Class of 2014 - B.A., Computer Science, Music minor

**INTERESTS** 

Live music, generative art, snowboarding, mountain biking.